You're not Gyeonwoo, you're Bongsu.
Ah, Seongya, why are you so scary?
Bongsu, what about Gyeonwoo?
Where is Gyeonwoo?
His body is completely
tell me how to have it
skin care
Just look at the blood, you're involved with a ghost
Ah, that would be perfect for a suicide ghost.
I'm sorry
Oh, Sang-moon has to see blood.
Sangmun...
Huh?
Seongya, let’s go first.
Wait a minute
Hey
You say you take care of a shaman?
If I let a suicidal demon go alone, will it be used?
- Hey
- Huh? no!
Let go of this!
ah!
Hey Gyeonwoo
Huh? Hey Gyeonwoo!
Huh?
Ah...
Gyeonwoo, are you okay?
Um... Yeah
It's okay
Thank goodness
Ah, but
No, but I don’t think you’re okay?
uh?
Ah...
Oh, I see.
Want a bike?
Yeah, just for today
Seongah is in a lot of pain.
I'm just trying to take you home
Yeah? Then I'll give you a ride
No...
Wait a minute, Seongya.
Hey! IC
Put it out when you say it
Didn't you already say it with words, did you do it with your feet?
Oh, I don’t know!
Oh, just give it to me!
uh? Bongsu, don’t do it!
Gyeonwoo, let’s just keep holding hands.
Jiho
Bongsu is a much worse kid than I thought.
Because I don't know what to do
Let's just get the bikes out quickly...
runner
hello
That's right
I was a nursing dog
Now
Bongsuya
Where is Gyeonwoo?
I...
I ate it
Cursing you?
You won't curse unless you have my stuff.
Stuff?
why do i drink
Am I not drunk?
I pity you, my friend.
You don't feel sorry for me, my friend.
What are you doing, what are you looking for?
What happened to the silver ring?
Has it already been returned to the original owner?
What does that have to do with you?
Is it yours?
how is it?
How do you feel about Sang-moon taking over your entire body?
Speak quietly, you are sleeping.
But where are you going?
Why are you dressed like this?
Come soon
What's coming so soon
don't come
Don't come?
No, but what kind of trick are you trying to pull?
uh?
Are you going to leave it like this?
For now
Know the direction you're flying
Let's set the net there.
This is Gogmasan Mountain
Maetoeya used by Bodhisattva Park
Who said something was possessed by a ghost?
You broke it so quickly?
I had a hard time finding it
People with money usually don't have time.
Write...
one, ten, one hundred, one thousand, ten thousand, one hundred thousand, one million, ten million
yes, thank you, yes
Is there anything else you want, sir?
No, thank you for your hard work.
Do you think you did well in making up with Dongcheon?
This is Dongcheon’s.
10 years ago
Here's what you bought me
mom
This is my mom's
Huh?
Ah, butterflies suit you
Look look, look
Ah, my mom is pretty.
You two were so pretty back then
A
Oh my god, what is this?
uh?
Why are you putting ghost cotton in the garden where butterflies play?
This is Dongcheon's work, right?
Ugh
Really sensible
Ghost face means evil death.
I guess there was a ghost I wanted to chase away.
maybe
Butterfly ghost?
Oh, I know I did something wrong too
Ah, but I don’t want to give it back!
How did you know how to steal my body?
Yeomhwa, his intentions are obvious, right?
After killing Gyeonwoo
Aren't you trying to create an evil spirit?
But to do that, what?
Because I have to take over Gyeonwoo’s entire body.
They told me right away?
Ah, but that's it, right?
Oh, I'm really with that person
We're not the same anymore
I want to live as a person
Ah, then what should I do with Chloride now?
Just stop it
I already blocked it once
I am not originally from that abandoned family.
It was in an object.
But I
As soon as I heard the news that he took over that body
You're asking me where that thing is.
I didn't tell you
You just said something right away?
I said it a little scary
When I scare you again
It's definitely a scary style.
I have no intention of becoming an evil spirit, huh?
Do you understand my feelings now?
Say something, old shaman.
haunted object
You found a treasure?
chloride
I'm looking for the treasure that the beacon water used to live in.
Destroy your treasures
The intention is to call the grim reaper.
Because Bongsu refuses to come out of Gyeonwoo’s body.
Forcing a cowherd
I'm trying to send you to the afterlife
So what should I do?
First of all, you have to protect the beacon.
Then what about Gyeonwu?
If you get caught by the grim reaper
Gyeonwoo is lost forever
Protecting the beacon is protecting Gyeonwoo.
How about another way?
Is there no other way?
Because I want to live as a person
Because I want to be by your side
They say they stole Gyeonwoo’s body.
That's to my ears
I heard you wanted to be loved
Take a good look at that heart
Don't be too hateful
Daughter
What does our shaman do?
It's soothing.
yes
Goods and talismans are tools
The essence is in the heart
If you take good care of my broken heart
everything happens
Everything is going as it should.
Still...
It takes too long
Still, I have to go the right way.
Hey
What happened to you?
Looking for a name?
Well, did you find it?
Why the sudden interest?
What did the old shaman say?
just
be nice to you
If you live, Gyeonherd also lives.
Are you going to be nice to me?
Yeah
what, how
How are you going to treat me well?
Don't be lonely
Anyone who is lonely turns into a ghost
Gyeonwoo, I'll put it back the right way.
Until then, please stay safe.
Hey there!
Is there anyone?
Oh, I don't know where it is
There is no road
Is it crying?
Yap
Hey, why are you like this? You see the kids
Are you saying you'll be nice to me?
huh?
Hey...
Wow, amazing, it looks like glutinous rice cake
Are you saying you'll be nice to me?
Well, it's the perfect height to rest your chin on.
ok
Are you two dating?
No, I like it one-sidedly.
It's unrequited love
What is it, a real man?
Hey
I stayed with Bongsu for too long.
Are you starting to resemble Bongsu?
Stay away!
Why are you acting like a beacon like this?
Um...
Is it Bongsu?
huh?
What is it?
I'm Bongsu, man.
That's not it
What about Gyeonherd? What is Gyeonwoo’s life like?
Having all your features taken away
It's really rare
The priority is to appease Bongsu first.
I will also start praying for 100 days starting today.
It takes 100 days?
Haha, I can't guarantee that either.
If not 100 days, 200 days
If not 200 days, 300 days
I have to pray and comfort you until it happens.
I can't wait that long
Hey, go in when you're talking
Quickly call Gyeonwoo
Hey, you really don’t say anything
What are you doing with your hands right now?
Hey!
Don't play around
Look at me
We're in the same group
What?
I like you guys
I like shamans
I want to stay together
But if you stretch out your hand to catch the shaman,
Go back to Gyeonherd
Let's go home, Seongya.
Even if he falls
I can't help you get up
Even if you cry, I can't wipe your tears away
That's too much
It was painful
really
Write, let’s pray together for 100 days, shall we?
Will it work, will it work?
Oh, okay!
I can't do it with the doctor, I lost.
- The game doesn't work.
- I saw it, I saw it.
Yeah, no.
Hey!
Why, why, why! what?
What about Park Seong-ah?
Park Seong-ah why!
no, that
Please say thank you
What fortune told me
No mouth?
Oh, you say it yourself!
I don't feel like talking right now
I'm depressed!
sad!
hey! Don't bother my friend!
what?
- Is it Joo-seung?
- huh?
Mr. Lee, are you crazy?
Hey, we're friends.
Where is he?
Ah, who are you talking about?
He was there then, Hwamok High School!
hey!
what?
- Isn’t that him back then?
- Harmony, harmony, harmony, harmony
What are you guys?
Can you hit me a little?
Hey
Hey, hey, hey, wait a minute!
Ah, okay, okay!
Okay, okay!
- This dog!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, catch it, catch it, aww, really!
Why are you holding me, why are you holding me!
- Stay still.
- Let go, don't let go!
Let go!
Hey, why did you stop me earlier?
I'm good at fighting
They are good at fighting too
Why are you guys getting beaten up?
Jinwoong is now
You can't have an accident
Why?
If you have an accident, your parents will be called.
He can't meet his mom now
oh
They say your mom threw it away in the family register?
Hey
I
I have to protect my mother by not meeting her.
From dad
Hey
Let's go home
- Hey!
- Yes
Why are you coming now?
The construction is done, I was busy.
Are you as pretty as ever today?
What are you saying, hurry up and go to your room?
Wait a minute
What is this, blood?
Yeah, we had a fight.
Did you fight?
Hey, what if you fight with Gyeonwoo’s body?
Athletes
Don't you know you shouldn't fight?
What if you get hurt...
I won't fight
Ah, shaman, do you know what?
what?
you
You're pretty even when you're angry
This is really
Hey!
Oh, I'm pissed, really.
Where did he go again?
There's so much fighting, starting in the morning, huh?
what?
Did you do archery? no way?
I have to do it, work hard.
When you think of archery, you mean Bae Gyeon-woo, and if you say Bae Gyeon-woo, you mean archery.
Get out of my way, I'm having a hard time
Ouch!
What are you doing, give it to me?
This bastard, help my girlfriend?
Hey, stay
Ha, indeed
Hey
Why, what?
Eat this
Man, it's really delicious.
It's really delicious, this is really good
-Why is he like that?
- hey! I...
Thanks, eh?
They say it’s so delicious
Just one candy
So happy like that
- Like a child
- Hey, this is better than what I ate yesterday.
It tastes so much better, hey!
what?
Ah, it's delicious
Sweet!
But honestly, you just got hit too.
What do you mean!
I treated you like a man
Hey, hey, hey, it shouldn't be like this
If you're going to do this, try arm wrestling.
- Come here.
- Arm wrestling? Okay, call
Hey, gang, come here
Come here, look at the referee, quickly.
-Why?
- You are the referee.
Now, if you say one, two, three, you're done.
One, two, three!
Hey, hey, hey!
Gyeonwoo’s mood has changed, right?
Oh, maybe something has become more attractive?
You look comfortable
I want to become friends
Shall we go to Konona together?
No, at best I am a child who has become comfortable.
Why are you trying to make me uncomfortable again?
Gyeonwoo, do you want to go to Kono together?
good!
ok
Oh, Bae Gyeon-woo, what’s going on?
- Great!
- Hey, not you.
- Not me?
- Are you going?
- What am I?
- Let's go first.
- later
-Why are you going to Kono all of a sudden?
everyone
I think I like Bongsu more than Gyeonwoo.
Shoveling? Kid...
It's the same face
How can they be so different?
Because it's a different person
It's not that I don't like Bongsu.
Do things you would never do if you were a Gyeonwoo
Because I do whatever I want
It's refreshing too
Oh my, it's cold, it's cold
But...
Because no one knows that Gyeonwoo is not Gyeonwoo.
Because I'm the only one who knows
I'm afraid that Gyeonwoo will be erased like this.
I'm afraid I'll disappear from the real world
I miss Gyeonwoo so much
No, you two can sing it.
Oh, how can I meet Gyeonwoo when I don’t have him!
You can sing it at congratulations.
Yes?
Chukshi
Huh?
Congratulations...
Hey Gyeonwoo
Hey, it's time to wake up
Are you Gyeonwoo?
uh?
who is this?
who is this!
come out
Yunboya
It's me
Brother!
Yunboya
- are you okay?
- Yes
You're not hurt, right?
Hey Gyeonwoo
Are you Gyeonwoo?
uh?
Seongya
Hey, Gyeonwoo!
Me... until just now
It was on a mountain, on a mountain, wasn't it?
It's in my memory
The soul that lost its body stays in memory.
So
I became friends with those soldiers.
I'm telling you to listen to the story, right?
Because I remember Bongsu.
One of the two will be a beacon.
Right?
Yeah
Why can't Bongsu ascend to heaven?
I need to know if he has become a ghost
Only then can you find a way to soothe that soul.
It's easy to find
I'll try it
Huh?
The celebration is over
Just wait, I'll be right back
Yeah, I'll wait.
Hey there
Guys?
Oh, it must be difficult to become friends?
I'm sure the silver ring belongs to an evil spirit.
How do I get this?
a talisman
Are you going to rob me without leaving a single piece behind?
Where are you, girl? I'll go
What's up with the demon?
Why is he asking about a demon?
he is so happy
Everyone else is worried
Fairy of Heaven and Earth was completely mentally broken.
Invoking ghosts during celebrations
You forgot?
Now that I know, I should have called you out.
I guess so
But why do you ask that...
I hung up, wow!
yes
What needs to be shaken
It's the heart
Hey Gyeonwoo!
Come here
Hey!
Let’s go to the selection competition, national team!
Oh, it's noisy
What? National University?
You wear this Taegeuk symbol on your chest, right?
wow!
kid, i mean
Nothing has happened yet
It will happen soon, something like that.
Hey, can I get your autograph in advance?
Uh, give it to me
Hey, me, me, me
Me here, do it here
Hey, it tickles.
Cool, cool, cool
The signature is unique, but?
Hey, cool, hey
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute
Hey...
- Hey
Why?
When I become a national team player, please grant me just one wish.
Wish?
What is your wish?
what?
you and me
Sir, let’s see if this is really true.
Why, where are you going?
Hey, who wants to do it now?
I was just talking about my wish.
No, you can't even talk?
Uh, don't say it, don't say it out loud.
You're talking nonsense, Mr.
Why doesn't this make sense?
I want to have my first kiss
I want to do that with you
What I desperately want
There's only one thing
Why doesn't it make sense to just say my wish?
I want to have my first kiss with Park Seong-ah!
Are you crazy?
why?
Do you want to kiss a shaman too?
Of course you want to do it
- Sorry for asking.
- Do you really want to die?
Unfortunately, I don't die easily.
Because his specialty is resurrection
But
Still, if you do this
Wouldn’t the shaman take a look at me at least once?
Because I have Bae Gyeon-woo’s face and Bae Gyeon-woo’s body again.
Isn't it?
Hey, Bae Gyeon-woo
To my father
You keep calling me
Father?
I guess Bae Gyeon-woo’s father isn’t there?
Where did you see that person?
Hey, it's really scary, but my skills are insignificant.
Are you using Bae Gyeon-woo’s family?
Did you use your head?
You did the hair first
You had a silver ring.
I will return it to its original owner.
Didn’t you wander the nine heavens with one embrace?
He said he would return it as soon as he got a human body.
Why do you still have it?
I've been a little busy
I have to become a national representative
Wow
Pretending to be a human must be quite fun.
Yeah, it's fun
I'm going to live like this for the rest of my life
You are so strong that you are on the verge of becoming an evil spirit.
Do whatever you want
I can't control it
So I thought about it
I have a hard time like this too
How difficult is it for Heaven and Earth Fairy?
Did you know that Sangmun can appear during congratulatory ceremonies?
During the celebration...
What comes out?
Bae Gyeon-woo is here?
As expected
I didn't know
Now he's a ghost
The celebration is his time.
Don't even tell me my country
A demon who stole a human body
I know when things will change
Do you want to become a person?
why?
When I become a person
Who even loves me?
How scary is it?
Just a shell of a person
If you keep pretending to be human
It's me, I only use one talisman
Without the power to write a talisman
As I became weaker
What kind of scheme are you planning all the time?
uh?
Hey
Take your time
Oh, you know, then
Is there anything more important to a mother than a baby?
what?
Write it quickly?
Okay
I'm always like this guy
I don't use it
Ah...
What are you doing here?
uh?
Uh...
Ah...
It's nothing
let's go
I'm welcome anytime
I'll wait at the abandoned house
Who are you?
You really don't have any friends?
I'm friends with this guy
Wow, it’s bloody, huh?
What is that guy?
It's nothing
Hey, let's go together
Heaven and Earth Fairy’s sincerity
Aren’t you curious?
Check it out for yourself
Hey Gyeonwoo
Hey, it's time to wake up
What is it?
Why do you look so sad?
my eyes are crying
Right? Uh...
Is it because I missed you so much?
me too
I missed you so, so much too
Oh, how about there?
Is it worth it?
Oh, did you become friends with those soldiers?
Did you find out which of the two is Bongsu?
why?
Have you become friends yet?
It can be
Still
We became friends quickly
I hope they find a way to relocate Bongsu.
Please send me a good beacon
You too come back to your place
Shaman
Shaman...
Bongsuya
Why are they in such a mood?
Attention, greet the teacher
Thank you!
very just
You have to finish class to come back alive.
Can’t dating be banned as a school rule?
I can't breathe, I can't live
Seongah, my hand must hurt.
We're all here
I was planning on letting it go anyway.
Why here?
stay here
the name I was looking for
Among the two student soldiers
I'm having a big baby
This little kid
Jang Yunboya
When Yunbo dies
The silver ring my mother gave me
He asked me to send him home instead of him.
I can't grant that request
Because I regret being dead
I became a ghost
Because I did it like this
My resentment will be relieved
Bongsuya
Now that I've solved one, the seal is over.
I'll live as Bae Gyeon-woo
Then what about Gyeonwu?
Bae Gyeon-woo?
He's already a ghost
Appears only during celebrations
Let's go now
Oh, no, hey, wait a minute.
- Hey
- Seong-ah, it hurts!
It hurts me too
Me too...
Are you here?
What about the talisman?
Girl, look at your temper.
Friend, are you breathing and living?
Wow, where does the smell of Cheonggukjang come from?
Does it sound like this?
The talisman!
It's there, right?
what?
Friend, I'm sorry.
Release it now
no matter how
Even if you lose your head
Are you thinking of calling the grim reaper somewhere?
The grim reaper descended without a list
How is this any different from a murderer?
You can kill anyone
It doesn’t matter how many people I kill!
Even evil spirits avoid anonymous messengers.
No matter how desperate it is, it's not like that.
So what?
What are you going to do?
A ghost in your body
The guy who pretends to give me his body
I'm going to take it off
No way
I hate it!
I hate it
No way
Don't do it!
uh?
Absolutely not! don't do it!
don't do that
I ask you this, don’t do that!
No, don't do it!
You stop being a shaman now.
don't do it
Don't do it, don't do it!
Don't...
Please do me a favor.
I did help, but
If it deviates that much
Letting go could be the way for both of us
Yeomhwa can't come back
I'm not holding you back.
Then?
I'm following him.
He won't let go of his children.
How can I let myself go?
I have to follow him wherever he goes.
Even if you cross the line?
I have to go
Cut off all my limbs again?
What about the baby?
What about my baby?
Are you afraid of lions?
Are you afraid of evil spirits?
no
What should you be most afraid of me?
A mother who lost her child?
What was stolen from you?
The ginseng that was given to me was scattered on the street.
Gyeonwoo really can’t come back?
Bongsu
If you decide to live as a cowherd
Gyeonwoo can't do anything and just
I have no choice but to lose my body?
I guess so?
Of course I have another way
Any other way?
Other people only know how to appease
I know how to scold you too
Quit archery?
What kind of bullshit are you talking about!
I'm not doing it, it's not fun, now
Then, are you on the national team?
The Olympics!
Oh, if you want to go out like that.
Either practice or the coach leaves!
- Boy...
-Where is this bastard?
uh?
Ouch!
- Ah!
- You're not standing there!
Yay!
Archery is a cowherd's dream
Who are you that you give up your dream of becoming a cowherd?
I'm sorry
The me in front of you is Bae Gyeon-woo
They say I'm giving up my dream
What does it matter to you?
You're not a Gyeonwoo, you're a Bongsu!
Don't call me Bongsu!
That's not my real name anyway.
Didn't you make it your own way?
I'm such a stranger now
I don’t want to live with a roughly made-up name.
you forward
If you don't call me Bae Gyeon-woo
Don't talk to me, okay?
Of course I have another way
The evil spirit has a silver ring.
bring it
Then the evil spirit will disappear
Hey, hey, stop it
Hey, don't do it!
Get out of the way!
I'm going to throw away my belongings!
Really, what are you!
uh?
thank you
What are you doing with it now?
That kind of thing
I'm asking before giving you a ring.
goodbye
Oh, hey!
hey!
Really, Mr.
What is this, huh?
Uh, Seongya.
What should I do?
I think I made a mistake
Hey
Hey, are you okay?
Bongsuya
Bongsu!
Ghost Lion, Lion’s Advent
Idiots, extermination of evil, salary regulation
Oh, kinda!
it hurts!
I got something precious
Yeomhwa will definitely call the grim reaper
Let's launch a diversionary operation.
I put up a barrier to hide the location of the beacon.
Seongah wears a silver ring.
- Go to the place where they were buried and perform an exorcism.
- Over there.
Hiding my identity here
Let’s perform a ritual for protection there.
The grim reaper in the wrong direction
It's tempting
There is a memorial service today
Get back!
Whoa!
Ghost Lion, Lion's Advent, Yosa Yomul
Extermination of evil nature, benefit rate ordinance
Demon King Lion, Lion's Advent, Ghostly Monsters
Designating the sun, avoiding sacrifice
Boa Wonsin, Goodbye to All, Salary and Benefits Regulations
Boa Wonsin, goodbye to all.
Designation of the sun, avoidance of sacrifice, Boa Wonsin, goodbye to all
Designating the sun, avoiding sacrifice, Boa Wonsin
Lion's Advent, Yosa Yomul
Extermination of evil nature, benefit rate ordinance
Boa Wonsin, goodbye to all.
- Designation of the sun, avoidance of sacrifice, Boa Wonsin
- Huh? hey!
Hey, over there!
There's a lion over there!
- Close your eyes!
- hey!
Aunt
Designating the sun, avoiding sacrifice
Boa Wonsin, Goodbye to All, Salary and Benefits Regulations
Salary benefit rate ordinance
Done
Let's go
Hey!
hey!
uh?
I...
Why do I have to suffer like this?
uh?
You just want to live?
I just want to live!
hate the world
by cursing a person
Those who are alive and become ghosts, be afraid.
How to defeat the devil
you can defeat it too
What has to die is chloride paper
Demon king lion, advent of the lion, evil spirits, extinction of evil spirits
Salary benefit rate ordinance, benefit rate ordinance
Salary and Benefits Ordinance, Sabaha
Who are you!
who is this?
Who makes the comeback?
Ghost Lion, Lion’s Advent
Extinction of evil spirits and evil spirits
Demon king lion, advent of the lion, evil spirits, extinction of evil spirits
Ha, something is wrong.
The lion turned
Demon King Lion, Lion Advent, Extinction of Evil!
No way
I can’t die like this!
I can't die like this
I can't even see my baby
come to mom
Demon King Lion, Lion's Advent, Ghostly Monsters
Salary benefit rate ordinance, benefit rate ordinance
Salary and Benefits Ordinance, Sabaha
Ghost face means evil death.
The human talisman is
How to get from person to person as a talisman
Objects with eyes, nose, and mouth
Give it as an alter ego.
Even if you can't reach it, you can protect it
Even if I can't reach it
can protect
Mother!
mother no
Why?
Why on earth?
I knew you would go to the end
So this time I waited at the end
Why?
Something like me...
Are you caught and put in this situation?
Did you say it?
I won't let go
Mom?
mom?
Uh...Mom!
Mom...
To exorcise evil spirits
The fairy of heaven and earth must die
He doesn't even know what he's doing!
Grant me just one wish.
Let's go on a date quickly
I know everything
He knows everything
I will definitely be back before graduation ceremony
It means the shaman is dead.
Seong-ah is not dead.
Seong-ya, wait.
I'll go now
If I find it, I will kill you.
Would you like to cooperate?
Go! Go quickly, Seong-ya!